[Music] Let's
[Música]
see family
a ver familia
please speak up hit him hit him hit him
hable por favor pegarle un toca éxito
hit him that medel guasa that has already
decirle que medel guasa que ya ha
lifted that let's see are they canceling
levantado eso a ver están cancelando
abi the girlfriend or ex girlfriend because these
a abi la novia o ex novia porque esta
people have
gente
already driven me crazy okay from orlov block
ya me tiene loco vale de orlov block
because I think it seems that they have
porque creo parece ser que la han
caught her a multi account okay it seems
pillado una multi cuenta vale parece ser
that they have caught her a multi account I don't
que la han pillado una multi cuenta no
know what they are basing it on because I am
sé en qué se basan porque me estoy
finding out the same one who directly with
enterando a la misma quien directo con
you so let's see leave a second
ustedes así que a ver dejar un segundo
because the thread that was being made
porque el hilo que se estaba realizando
itself is this one it
en sí es éste
says I present to you the secondary account
dice os presento a la cuenta secundaria
of abbey who seems to be the apprentice
de abbey quien parece ser la aprendiz
of choca well the apprentice of choca
del choca bueno la aprendiz del choque
one day and I already told you this when the
un día y esto ya se lo dije cuando lo
chocas thing too but one day when I
del chocas también pero un día cuando
go through some issues that we have I will be able to
pase unos temas que tenemos os podré
tell you
contar
a case that is much worse of multiple
un caso que es muchísimo peor de multi
accounts a case that is much worse
cuentas un caso que es muchísimo peor
with more shamelessness
con más descaro
that he believes that he is not that he believes that he is not from
que se cree que no que se cree que no de
Alicante and that it is not noticeable but come on now
alicante y que no se nota pero vamos ya
I will tell you okay I present to you the
ya os contaré vale os presentó la cuenta
secondary account of experto who seems to be the
secundaria de hábil quien parece ser la
apprentice of choca literally  all of
aprendiz del choca literalmente todos
his tweets are replies defending
sus tweets son respuestas defendiendo a
that girl it's also twitter for iphone it
esa chica también es twitter for iphone
also has the initial capital letter
también tiene la mayúscula inicial
disabled he insults just like her
desactivada insulta igual que ella
or rather the initial capital letter disabled
o sea la mayúscula inicial desactivada
I didn't even know
ni sabía yo
habib and piqué does with that account or
habib y piqué hace con esa cuenta o
not
no
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music] it does
[Música]
n't matter that they go for a wipe
no importa que vayan por una toallita
to clean my ass
para limpiarme el culo
and I
y
really don't know why you see me I don't know I don't
realmente no sé por qué me veis yo no sé
know why I have viewers guys I
no sé por qué tengo espectadores tíos
really really don't know why I have
realmente realmente no sé por qué tengo
viewers
espectadores tiempo
lamentable lamentable lamentable time
lamentable lamentable
how you caught me with
lamentable como me habéis pillado con
this it's
esto es
we like now the overlay ok
nos gusta ahora el overlay ok
and so we stay still for the
y así nos estamos quietos para lo
real thing
verdadero
and so we stay 500 don't
y así nos quedamos 500 no
listen to me
escúchame
edwin creativity that yes they have never
edwin creatividad que sí que no te han
seen a live of yours in your life and that he has
visto un directo suyo en la vida y que
never touched a woman that yes well
jamás ha tocado una mujer que sí
to be a girl and becomes independent
pues para ser una niña y se independiza
219 days you want dear
219 día quieres caro
that you are like this in the account of whom I
que eres así en la cuenta de quien yo
speak that I will tell you one day like this but not
hablo que os contaré un día así pero no
only like this but with many more
solamente así sino con muchos más
indications it is
indicios
spoken with among its multiple ones it is
se habla con entre sus múltiples está
only retweets whatever are compliments to
solamente retuitea lo que sean piropos a
herself and only repeat anything that is
sí misma y solamente repita cosa que sea
against her enemy is to many
en contra de su enemigo es a muchos
indications let's go you can't another person
indicios vamos no puedes otra persona
because otherwise and if they have to
pues de otra manera y si se han de
tell the useful but I can't yet
contaron lo útil pero no puedo todavía
well I can't I would tell it but well it's better not
bueno no puedo yo lo contaría pero bueno
no let's see what else and
preferible que no no a ver qué más y
also her friend the pimp [ __ ] of the best
además su amigo el chulo [__] del mejor
said that the girl has like two or
dijo que la chavala tiene como dos o
three locks well here you have one I'm
tres candados pues aquí tenéis una estoy
screaming he's deleting all his tweets
chillando está borrando todos sus tweets
screenshots let's see since he's deleting
capturas a ver ya que está borrando
all the tours and I'll leave a record of
todos los tours y dejaré constancia de
some screenshots let's see wait I'm going to
algunas capturas a ver espera lo voy a
look at it before without letting me look at it
mirar antes sin dejarme que lo mire
before and without sharing the screen because
antes y sin compartir pantalla porque
twitter is dangerous not
twitter es peligroso no
the entire platform that advertising is
toda la plataforma que esa publicidad es
having fat goals for having been carried away
tener metas gorda por haberse dejado
by famous people were a game it's that it's that they
llevar por famosos eran jugada
are things that she is her
es que es que son cosas que ella es ella
or rather that she said
o sea que ella dijo
or rather that Lorena was one of your multiple
o sea que lorena era una de tus multi
accounts disappointed face really useful
cuentas cara decepcionada en verdad til
single uncle summer I have a son or anything
soltero tío verano tengo hijo ni ná
jp you will be seeing fact javi attention to
jp estarás viendo hecho javi atención a
twitter not exactly I was
twitter no precisamente me estaba
remembering jp because this girl
acordando de jp porque esta muchacha
this girl is not the one in the
esta muchacha no es la que sale en el
banana  green johann planas
guineo verde johann planas
this girl appears in the green wine joan
esta muchacha sale en el vino verde joan
plana no,
plana no
well she commits a [ __ ]
la pues ella comete un [__]
that if cool [ __ ] that you have never eaten
que si chulo [__] que no te has comido
a [ __ ] in your life I don't know what but she
un [__] en tu vida no sé qué pero ella
always depending on her in the same
siempre dependiendo de la de la misma
way to herself okay look one thing
forma a ella misma vale mirad una cosa
okay and go I
vale y va
think this girl appeared in the name
creo que esta chica salía en el nombre
of joan plana because joan plana messed
de joan plana porque joan plana se metía
with her or said that she always went with a low
con ella o decía que siempre iba con
neckline
escote
when they put and don't see on the internet when
cuando ponen y no ven en internet cuando
this is an achievement of positioning is
esto es un logro de posicionamiento es
when it says that and don't see on youtube the
cuando pone que y no ver en youtube lo
first thing that appears to you I
primero que te aparece
defended her
la defendí
I think it would be around here more or less
creo que sería por aquí más o menos
but I don't know what about the hatches it
pero no sé qué de las escotillas
was I don't know what about the ocote
era no sé qué del ocote
that was the parts to the necklines
que estaba las partes a los escotes
also it said there is a piece of video of
además ponía hay un trozo de vídeo de
the chicken from youtube but I think that if
del pollo de youtube pero creo que si
she
ella
but I don't remember in which part she came out of
pero no me acuerdo en qué parte salía
the wine see I do
del vino ver
n't remember in which
no me acuerdo en qué
section of the wine let's see it was an
sección del vino a ver era
ally without women it is magic I do
aliado sin féminas es magia
n't remember in which part of the novel
no me acuerdo en qué parte de la novela
this is a gem
esto es una joya
but if we have been 30 without insurance
pero si llevamos 30 sin seguro
and almost 15 99
y casi 15 99
1529 what
1529 qué
nothing do
nada
n't see you have a brutal memory yes
no veas tienes una memoria brutal sí
because when I saw these photos of them I
porque al ver estas fotos de ellas me
remembered but coats of minutes
acordaba pero abrigos de minutos
but when he got into the cleavage of the
pero cuando se metía en el escote de la
girl who was but don't stay the cleavage
chica que era pero no se quede el escote
of the girl chivas
de la chavala chivas
but find out the whole minute no in
pero averiguar todo el minuto no de
fact he didn't
hecho no
find out the minute of that
averiguó el minuto de eso
I don't care
me da igual
look here here here with the [ __ ] it was
mira aquí aquí aquí con la gilada era
safe I'm not going to miss anything anyway
seguro no me va a faltar nada igual
we go back to the book now come on here let's
volvemos al libro ahora no venga acá
see this
vemos esto
[Music]
[Música]
it can't be true the catch is
es que no puede ser verdad la pillada es
from a small child he doesn't follow anyone 300
de niño pequeño no sigue a nadie 300 me
likes given of which 280 are to
gustas dados de los cuales son 280 a
javi the answer that he deleted
javi la respuesta que ha borrado
defending had more clear water
defendiendo a había más claro agua
and well it goes without saying the nothing to do with
y bueno sobra decir los nada que ver con
the case of the crash it is not the same to
el caso del chocar no es lo mismo
defend yourself from barbarities like the
defenderse de barbaridades como lo de
red guard than to insult children who
guardia rojo que insultar a niños que te
tell you that they play lol badly for having
dicen que juegan mal la lol por tener
secondary accounts for that it is still
cuentas secundarias para eso sigue
something that seems murky to me and
siendo algo que a mí me parece turbio y
the people who are going to respond to
la gente que está yendo a responder
barbarities work is deleting tweet I
barbaridades obra está borrando tweet no
am not giving  somersaults that
estoy dando volteretas laterales que
well I'll tell you I'll tell you a
pues ya os contaré ya os contaré yo una
good one to increase it a good one if you
una buena de aumentar ello una buena si
want no longer lack law or one I'll
desean no ya falta ley o una ya os
tell you a good one a
contaré una buena
good one let's see it's not the same at the
una buena a ver no es lo mismo de
moment it's not the same because [ __ ]
momento no es lo mismo porque [__]
but followers and only followed rust it's
pero seguidores y sólo seguido óxido
not the same because [ __ ] let's
no es lo mismo porque [__]
see account those god I'm not
a ver cuenta a esos dios yo es que no me
going to create an account it's just that I don't
voy a crear una cuenta solo pasa que no
give a [ __ ] what they say about me
me importa una [__] lo que digan de mí
sanz plan let them say whatever they want that's it don't
sanz plan que digan lo que les dé la
be like that I want to answer
gana ya está no sea así quiero responder
something side from mine if there's something that they
algo lado desde la mía si hay algo que
don't put it easy for me like a good
no me lo ponen a huevo como una buena
answer that we laugh or something like that you
respuesta que nos riamos o algo por el
know but today I'm lazy to create
estilo sabe pero hoy me da pereza crear
a multi account I don't
una multi cuenta no
think I've ever had any death
creo que nunca he tenía ninguna muerte
account I think I've never I think that the
cuenta creo que nunca creo que las
only times that I used 50 have
únicas veces que yo utilizamos 50 han
been
sido
when the leader of the allies that
cuando el líder de los aliados que me
a boy left me one that seems like it was
dejó un chico una que parece que era
paper rent of pass that it was and then the
papel alquilo de pase que fue y luego la
girl this soul that left me the account
chica esta alma que me dejó la cuenta
to identify it trader very flat and I
para identificarlo trader bien plana y
think that it is I
creo que está
'm not sure if this was one of my
no estoy seguro si era esto la de mis
kids but for that  I could
chavalería pero para que yo me pudiera
create an account after I was
crear cuenta después de que me
suspended I think they
suspendiera
gave me an older account
creo que me dieron una cuenta más
than the one they suspended I don't
antigua de la que habían suspendido no
know what the deal was but I think
sé qué qué movida era pero creo que la
mine is verified I think
mía de ahora la dejo verificada creo que
in the past it was someone's multi-account I
en el pasado era una multi cuenta de
'm not sure don't listen to me
alguien no estoy seguro no me hagáis
don't turn off the case because I'm not sure
no apaga el caso porque no estoy seguro
if I created it with the vpn from scratch or something like that
si la cree con el vpn de cero o algo así
and it was my kids' one that I can't
y fue la de mis chavalería la que yo no
find the thing about the cleavages
encuentro lo de los escotes
because of the cleavage meeting dude
por encuentro de los escotes tío
look here I was defending myself by reading
fíjate aquí yo defendía yo al hacer leer
because I find the one with the hot guy's records I
porque encuentra la de los discos de tío
wanted to clear up the doubt if
bueno me quería quitar la duda de si
this girl was Abi she is or not
esta chica era la abi está o no
here she is here and here she is here is it is
aquí es aquí y aquí es aquí es si es
miracielo see and i' Joan Plan was
miracielo ve and i' el joan plan estaba
accusing this one of having too much cleavage
acusando a ésta de lleva mucho escote
they say she doesn't have cleavage the first one well
dicen que no tiene escote la primera
yes the careless ones take an eye out
pues sí los descuidados saca un ojo
because it happens if you have cut these issues
porque pasa si tienes corte estos temas
and criticize women like for example
y critica a las mujeres como por ejemplo
this one who blames her for having grown up
a esta no que la achaca de haber crecido
on the tweet platform for showing her
en la plataforma de tweet por enseñar su
cleavage when really we go to the
escote cuando realmente nos vamos al
girl's channel and in most
canal de la chica y en la mayoría de
cases she doesn't even put it  cleavage that we
ocasiones ni siquiera se pone escote que
could thank Sheffield for being her
podríamos gracias sheffield de serlo su
body but there showing everything note the
cuerpo pero ahí enseñando todo nótese la
irony for the love of god here three
ironía por el amor de dios aquí tres
quarters of the same plus t-shirt and another one
cuartos de lo mismo más camiseta y otra
I there at that moment I didn't know who
yo hay en ese momento no sabía quién era
the girl was I knew it later look at
la chica lo supe después fíjate de mira
that she was still I still is but I hadn't
que seguía yo aún lo es pero no había
done well the girlfriend never the
hecho bien cuenta la novia nunca los
times that caught 'in or people
tiempos que pillada 'in o gente
what caught na
qué pillado na
[Music]
[Música]